so estimate about how much money or with
the components cost just to just to
start out to play with it probably
figure about a hundred hundred fifty
dollars you've got to cut the stainless
steel plates I have some of you guys if
somebody wants to I have a whole bunch
of them of the six by six squares
somebody wants to buy some I just have
you know just the money into the the
shearing of it but if you guys want to
just buy stainless steel plates and
shear them off that's whatever if you've
got a machine shop local they can do
that that works pretty well back in my
joe sell days when i was really focused
on that there was quite a bit of talk
about when you cut the metal that you
get some magnetization of the metal of
going on do you have to be careful about
that kind of stuff using a conventional
joe cell which has the concentric
stainless steel tubes you do have to
worry about that that's actually fairly
easy to overcome with browns gas because
you can you can heat it
take out the take out the magnetism
shearing it or or cutting this cutting
the shapes out with a with a water jet
as because i use i use flat parallel
plates instead of the concentric
stainless steel tubes because I can
control the distances much better so
when you share them there's there's less
of an issue with that plus you know
there's magnetism there's para magnetism
and then there's diamagnetism and so I
one of the actually a couple of the free
energy devices that I've seen actually
relies upon a ratio between the three
levels of magnetism both pair magnets
and diamagnetism
and magnetism in in very ratios and what
they were able to tune the machines to
not just the components but everything
around the machine to the ratios of more
paramagnetism than than the others but
with different ratios they were able to
achieve free energy so met some some
amount of magnetism is good I haven't
actually run into an issue where the
magnetism in the system is a detriment
right now because I don't work with this
conventional there the concentric
stainless steel tubes and the concentric
tubes are usually what you see in a Joe
cell so that Joe cell is not necessary
for this it's one of the things where it
shows up but it's not necessarily a
crucial component let me back up here
the conventional Joe cell that we see
which is the conventional is perfect
concentric stainless steel tubes is a
sip is one tight above Joe cell if you
look at the books that have been written
on Joe cell technology and I actually
gave a lecture on this about five years
ago if you look at the the the books and
the information on that what you're
really looking for is certain types of
materials interacting with other types
of materials so you're looking for
metallic and as this also goes back to
Oregon research you're looking for
metallic versus natural materials some
Joe cells I have a I have a battery and
literally looks like a battery it's made
out of brass plates and a different type
of fluid in there and it is and it
conforms to all the rules of a Joe cell
it's just not made out of the concentric
stew or like the Mojo cell a sphere
which is really fun to play with but
it's but it actually conforms to all the
rules of the dough cell certain ratios
to height to width and the fluid the
fluid in there versus the metal
that's interacting with so there are
different types of Joe cells that the
concentric stew this only is only one of
them so is this going to be a science
where you can follow a recipe and like
for example if you were to mass-produce
something like this you can make it the
same way every time and it works the
same way every time or is there
something that goes interesting
materials where you require a gift to do
some tuning and now chemical gift for
example I have on this in this aspect
it's behaving the same way each time and
I'm not I'm not running into you know
times of day
I'm not running into the attitude of the
operator which I have machines that are
at that work absolutely contingent on
the attitude and the spiritual mindset
of the operator but this is this is
behaving a little bit different way and
I think we've it's a refinement of the
process that allows us to focus the the
energy without worrying about without
wearing too much about the outside
extraneous input now I haven't I can't
rule out the zodiacal signs or where the
moon is which is actually very important
in some processes some prospect
it's important to make a lot of
scientific processes they cannot machine
the plutonium course for nuclear nuclear
bombs or nuclear reactors they cannot
machine them under certain signs of the
moon because if they do
the metal will literally change
dimensions as the moon shifts they have
to do they have to machine them under
certain signs that are what they call
fixed otherwise the middle will change
dimensions and not work properly and
this has talked about in people who are
in that industry it is it is a
little-known fact in the industry yeah
something they don't dare talk about was
it was like to most people because it
kind of flied kind of flies in the face
of conventional physics that's a that's
a very strange and very understand
people who make automobile parts or like
engines for example for racecars that
when they make that they can make three
engines under seemingly identical
circumstances but they have to test each
one of them because they don't actually
function the same that's amazing and it
has to do with when they were made and
and it's there's really no such thing as
two identical scientifically made things
because there are other phenomena going
on it's not just humans that are
responsive to astrological types of
influences that materials also have an
input you're saying that you absolutely
in this particular process you haven't
noticed yet that kind of influence well
I haven't noticed that a macrocosmic
skill that may be happening on a micro
cosmic scale but you know it's funny you
mentioned that because when I was in
studying electrical engineering they
told us the same thing about things like
solar panels and I integrated circuits
and they actually have to put in they
actually have to engineer in adjustment
so that they can tune something into the
that they want and from a religious
perspective we we see that all energy
has consciousness and if we're working
with certain types of energy we have to
understand that the the consciousness of
that energy is going to come into play
but on a macro cosmic scale with this
hydrogen system that I've been working
with and we're not seeing it we're not
seeing a lot of influence in that regard
which makes me happy because because it
means that that everybody can work with
it and everybody can play with it so
that's exciting so it may not be
necessary that the person have an
alchemical calling so to speak to do
this or do you think how important do
you think that would be well because I'm
very much out chemically oriented and so
I'm probably not the not the norm of the
people that are going to be we're going
to be working with this I learned
something very interesting conventional
engineering deals with the bell curve
they want to know what goes on in this
in this normal space okay and they plot
all their diagrams and everything and
they create bell curves because they
want to understand what goes on in this
normal space I realized that is so far
outside of my kingdom understand because
I don't care what goes on there because
that's that's normal I want to know why
this little spike occurred over here I
want to know what goes on outside of the
norm so that's that's plenty a funny way
to look at it but that's that's where
I'm at and turn that into a new norm
[Music]
honing on that yeah so we didn't finish
the question about what would be
involved in getting started in this just
on an on a replication basis to prove to
yourself that it works we talked about
materials what about time
if you'll mechanically or if your hands
on or into you know about a week to put
this all together a week full time or
tinkering time a week tinkering time
yeah hobby time in the evening when you
come home for work yeah just playing
around with it you can sit and put
together the you can sit and put
together the plates pretty easily there
there's some rules you have to follow
and so you know you don't what
say this is the this is the thing about
working with working with hydrogen you
follow the rules to understand the rules
and you learn where you can break them
okay but you when you first start out
you reproduce things exactly the way
they're made before once you understand
the rules then you can start
experimenting outside of the rules do
you have on your website some kind of a
set of plans - no nothing nothing I just
have a few pictures up there right now I
just literally just barely got control
of that website again from from the
person who was running it before so a
real good guy but he kind of disappeared
down in Mexico and is exploring the the
ancient ruins down there which makes it
very difficult to you know run a
computer and state website it's the
phones I just got control of that so I
can post so I can start changing the
content again okay and let's
do you want to give you contact
information or can people go to the
website to get that people can go to the
website my the easiest way to contact me
is either through Facebook or my email
Earth's Earth's ransom at yahoo.com
that's dar THS ra n som at yahoo.com or
just look me up on Facebook and
communicate that way pretty easily too
important those are the easiest ways I
tempted to to bring up what you post on
Facebook the other day about a six-foot
rattles oh well you know I I have been
blessed with different messengers
through my through my life and I was
attacked by a six-foot rattlesnake the
other day that was a pretty pretty
interesting experience and it struck at
me twice and missed both times so it's a
it's a beautiful little miracle that I
am here and but that was a that was a
sign of change and actually in
retrospect that was an interesting
little warning that I had that I
received so I'm glad that it happened
you know I I did have to kill the
rattlesnake but because it was very
aggressive and was not just you know
hanging out by himself and doing nothing
he was
actually very aggressive so it was it
was a indicator that certain things were
changing for me which happens the last
time was a bear
five years ago broke into my house
teaching me an interesting lesson that I
got to that I had to learn interesting
well thanks for sharing that is there
anything else in this particular sector
that we haven't talked about that ought
to be brought up oh you know I'm sure
there is but we but as you know when we
start looking at the machine such I'll
start thinking of more stuff all right
so let's do that as part three okay and
we'll we'll stop this segment for now
all right well plates instead of the
concentric stainless steel tubes because
I can control the distances much better
so when you shear them there's there's
less of an issue with that plus you know
there's magnetism there's para magnetism
and there's diamagnetism so estimate
about how much money or with the
components cost wheels just to just
start out to play with it probably
figure about a hundred hundred fifty
dollars you've got to cut the stainless
steel plates I have some if you guys if
somebody wants to do I have a whole
bunch of them of the six by six squares
somebody wants to buy some I just have
you know just the money into the the
shearing of it but if you guys want to
just buy stainless steel plates and
shear them off that's whatever if you've
got a machine shop local they can do
that back in my joe sell days when I was
really focused on that there was quite a
bit of talk about when you cut the metal
that you get some magnetization of the
metal of going on do you have to be
careful about that kind of stuff using a
conventional joe cell which has the
stainless steel tubes you do have to
worry about that that's actually fairly
easy to overcome with Browns gas because
you can you can heat it and take out the
take out the magnetism sharing it or or
cutting this cutting the shapes out with
a with a water jet is because I use I
use flat pair